[QUACKING]
[WARBLE, ZAP!]
[ROARS]
♪ "Adventure Time" ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the Dog and Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's "Adventure Time" ♪
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
[CLEARS THROAT]
Okay, so here's what happened.
I had sent my top
employee, Rennie Hamlin,
to check on one of my properties...
Okay, boss, I'm here now.
Joshua and Margaret Investigations!
Yep, there's definitely been a break-in.
Check out the damage.
I'll call you back in 30 seconds.
[KEYS JINGLE]
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
Rennie?
[STAMMERING]
And he's been like this ever since.
Poor guy.
Something terrifying has taken residence
in Joshua and Margaret's old office,
and it's not paying rent.
So I want you guys to find out
what it is and get it out.
Yes, sir, son!
You have one hour!
Bye, Dad.
I wonder what it could be.
Maybe it's a gross rotting fish god
with long, slimy tentacles.
Maybe it's a teenage
silverware werewolf squatter.
Hey, you know what it could be?
It could be a ghost.
I think I saw a ghost
there when I was a baby.
Maybe it's like a ghost hotspot.
Ghosts, huh?
Whoa, wait! What if it's...
BOTH: Ghost Mom and Dad!
I have to brush my hair!
I'll go get tulips for Mom!
Man, I've never been this
excited about ghosts before.
This could be one more
chance to tell Mom and Dad
how much we love them.
And show 'em that their
kids are awesome.
JAKE: Hello? Ghosts?
If you're in here, please
vacate my son's property!
Unless you're Mom and Dad ghosts!
Yeah, in that case, I brought flowers!
Look. There's the broken window.
But I don't see any signs
of squatters... or ghosts.
I'll sniff 'em out.
[SNIFFING]
Hey, Jake,
why don't we own this place?
I dunno. Kim Kil Whan
is a good businessman.
Plus I'd feel kinda weird
dealing with this stuff.
Yeah. Just looking at all this
is like, "Whoa, memories!"
Like this ticker tape machine.
Remember when Mom and
Dad brought us to work
and we made a fort of ticker tape?
It was right over there!
And over here you gave me
a wet willie one time.
Ew, no, I didn't.
Right. I know you believe that's true,
but memories distort over time.
Classic false memory syndrome.
Maybe you're the one with
a false memory syndrome.
Classic false memory syndrome response.
[TICKING]
You hear that?
Can you use your dog powers
to locate that sound?
Way ahead of you, pal.
Uh... over there!
Aha!
[TICKING STOPS]
Anything?
Nope. This is a nice bathroom, though.
Man, this whole office is nice.
It's kinda bunk how Mom
and Dad stopped using it.
Yeah, it's weird that they
had this whole other life,
and they just dropped it for us babies.
We were babies forever. Man, we suck.
Yeah, but they knew what
they were getting into.
Whoa!
Who moved the sofa?
Who put forth those chairs?!
Who set the table?!
What's going on?!
This griz is poltergeist biz.
But I don't want that.
Embrace the paranormal, bro.
Are these candles real or
poltergeist mind-tricks?
[TAPE RATTLING] Look!
BOTH: Poltergeist!
[TAPE WHIRRING]
MARGARET: Ooh, goody. It's on now, dear.
Well done, Margaret, love.
BOTH: Dad! Hello, future people.
I'm Joshua of Joshua and
Margaret Investigations.
And behind the camera you have my
lovely wife and partner, Margaret.
- Hello.
- We're making this tape
to document the strange
phenomena in our new office.
Like this weird message
spelled out in...
[PAPER RUSTLES] Oh, applesauce.
You've really stepped
in it now, darling.
Indubitably.
But something is definitely
trying to chat us up,
and we're gonna catch it on film.
I got this fancy
ghost-hunting doohickey.
It's supposed to record EVPs and such.
[TICKING] [GASPS]
Gracious, there it is!
Margaret! Margaret! There's
another one over here!
[SCREAMS]
Dude! This place is full of ghosts!
[WIND HOWLS]
We should split up and see if
we can get them to appear.
I'll take the bathroom!
That's the spirit.
Hmm. "Spirit."
[WINGS FLAPPING, INSECTS CHIRPING]
Maybe Mom and Dad left some
books about ghost hunting.
Hmm.
[TICKING]
[GASPS] A ghost!
It seems like the ticking sound
precedes each ghost encounter.
Okay, Finn, what ticks?
Metronomes, bombs, pencils.
[CHATTERING]
The bathroom is a lot scarier
than I was expecting.
[TICKING]
[SCREAMS]
Hearts, egg timers, typewriters.
[THUDDING]
- What else?
- [TICKING]
[WHOOSH]
Whoa, lil' ghost babies!
Wait, that's baby Jermaine!
And baby Jake!
And baby me!
Babababa!
[CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLES] Oh, yeah?
Oh! Yip! Yip! Yip! Yip!
[LAUGHS]
Oh, snap. I guess it was me.
Hold on. These babies ain't
ghoulish ghosts at all.
They're like time...
disto... to... morphs?
Hmm.
[CLATTERING]
JAKE: Scared?
No way! I'm primitive! I'm real!
Ghosts, you can't touch this dog!
You've got ethereal hands!
I'm alive! I'm filled with hot blood!
You'll never see through me!
Gotcha, ghoul!
Pardon?
Aah!
Oh, sorry for interrupting your poop.
Hey, sorry again, man,
but I have a qu...
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
I gotta get out of here!
No, Jake. You gotta stay
for your boy Kim Kil Whan.
Ghost! Quit freeloading off my son!
That's a father's job!
JOSHUA: [STRAINED] Margaret, stay away!
Huh?
Something's about to happen!
Dad?
So, I can see you, and you can see me.
And we're occupying the same space now.
So this time stuff must
be getting more intense.
Whoa!
[EXHALES]
Hey, creeper, stop
creepin' on baby Jake!
Baby Jake?
Finn! I'm freaking out, man!
I just saw the most messed-up thing!
Dad?
Margaret, stay away!
Something's about to happen!
MARGARET: Something's about
to happen with me, too!
Margaret! Aah!
[SPLAT!]
Yowzas!
[SINGING] Hello, Daddy! Hello, Mommy!
It's so nice to be here with you now!
That's so not how I was birthed!
I'm no melon baby! I'm
a majestic womb baby!
Jake, calm down.
I'm gonna go hog-wild on
the next ghost I see!
[KEYS JINGLE]
Boy, do I love real estate!
[GASPS] Aah!
[SCREAMS]
Aah!
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
KIM KIL WHAN: Rennie? [STAMMERING]
We're trapped in a ghost trap!
Relax, bro. There's no ghosts.
What we're experiencing are time slips.
Point is, something is causing this.
[TICKING, GLASS SHATTERS]
♪
You ready?
Time dingalings!
[TICKING] Wait, that ticking.
I know who this is!
Clock Bear!
One of the dudes that escaped
Dr. Gross' menagerie.
He must be the one
causing the time slips.
There's us from before.
[GROANS]
Are you sick?
Yeah, I'm pretty disgusted
with the whole situation!
I meant Clock Bear.
[GROANS]
[CLICKING]
[FWOOM!]
He's sucking up all the spilled time!
- That doesn't sound scientific!
- [WIND WHISTLING]
[GASPS] Jake, take care of Clock Bear.
There's something I gotta do!
Wait, I'm still confused!
And having feelings!
[WHISTLING, TICKING CONTINUE]
Oh, boy, our first case!
Looks like we have a poltergeist!
And it's got a little crush on me.
What a sassafrass!
Gotta get this on tape!
Whoops!
If this was all time weirdness,
I guess that memory was true.
I did see my own birth. Far out.
Oh!
Must be a leftover time ghost.
♪
Hmm.
We have to leave!
We're doin' what now?
It was just Clock Bear.
No, I don't think he has any money.
FINN: Jake? Jake!
Oh, no! Something's happened to Jake!
He could be in grave dang...
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
Okay, then.